tfod.in 2014-10-02

# 

www.tfod.in (TFOD™, abbreviation for The Future of Design™) is Conceptualised by M/s. ADD Ideas and designed, hosted & maintained by Imap Systems Pvt. Ltd (hereinafter referred to as ‘ISPL’ / ‘Imap Systems’). TFOD / ISPL is committed to safeguarding its users' privacy. Henceforth in this document TFOD will mean TFOD and ISPL, for all practical purposes. We request all our users to read the following 'privacy policy' to understand how their personal & business information will be treated, as they make full use of our services to their benefit. This policy is applicable only to the entire network of marketplaces operated by TFOD / ISPL and not by any other company. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the TFOD / ISPL Terms of Use. By your use of and/or registration on TFOD, you expressly consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy.

This policy is effective December 1st, 2013.

### Collection of Information

TFOD / ISPL collects information from its users when they register to gain access to our services or at other specific instances when they are requested to provide us with their personal & business information.

During registration, we ask the users for their name, email address, business information and other personal details. Once a user registers, he/she is no longer anonymous to TFOD / ISPL and it is deemed that the user has given TFOD / ISPL the right to publish the desired business & personal details throughout its marketplaces, including but not limited to, business directory, trade leads, catalogs etc.

We collect and store the following information:

Email address, IP address, and physical contact information;

StyleFiles, comments, reviews, images, other uploaded content, questions and answers, discussion, area posts and other messages, including correspondence between TFOD and you; and other information automatically collected whenever you interact with TFOD, such as computer sign-on data, invite friends, statistics on page views and traffic to and from the TFOD site. For example, we may use ‘cookies’ (small data files that are placed on your computer) so that we can recognize your browser and record such interaction information. You can disable the use of cookies through your browser settings, however this may affect your ability to use certain features of the TFOD site.

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 16. If you are under the age of 16, please do not use the TFOD site or services.

When you are on our network and are asked for personal information, you are sharing the information with TFOD / ISPL, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. Promotions that run on our network may be sponsored by companies other than TFOD / ISPL or may be co-sponsored by TFOD / ISPL and another company. Some or all data collected during a promotion may be shared with the sponsor. However, you can decide not to participate in the promotion if you don't want your data to be shared.

We also gather usage statistics such as pages viewed, number of unique visitors, browser software, screen resolution etc. for analysis that helps us provide you improved user experience and services.

### Use of Personal & Business Information

TFOD / ISPL will use this obtained information, 

  * \- to provide TFOD services;
  * \- to verify your identity when you sign in;
  * \- to encourage safe online experiences for our users and to enforce our policies;
  * \- to customize users' experience, analyze site usage, improve and measure interest in our services and inform users about services and updates;
  * \- to identify your reviews as your own;
  * \- to communicate administrative announcements when we need to provide users with information that may affect their use of TFOD;

Imap Systems's primary goal in collecting personal or public information is to provide the user with a customized experience on our network of sites. This includes personalized services, interactive communication and other services, most of which are completely free and remaining are paid. Business information is used to display the user's business listing or product offerings across our network to fetch maximum business opportunities for the user. 

User agrees that TFOD / ISPL will moderate / evaluate every upload whether text, images or audio /video for it’s content and acceptable content will be allowed to remain on the website, for public search or otherwise. Content not fitting into TFOD standards will not be allowed to be part of the Gallery and may remain part of individual profile only. Completely objectionable content will be removed from the website with or without communication with the user. User agrees that due to moderation process content uploaded on the personal profile may take a while to reach gallery section. 

In order to provide free services, TFOD / ISPL displays advertisements based upon the site usage statistics and visitor trends. TFOD / ISPL uses user's personal & business information to serve targeted advertisements through its websites, newsletters and customized mailers. In addition to it, once the user's personal and business information is displayed on our network, the user may start receiving business enquiries through email, phone or normal mail, from various buyers and sellers that might or might not be of their interest. TFOD / ISPL does not exercise any control over its users who may send business enquiries to the listed members. 

### Sharing of Information as a general rule

The Data collected may be shared in following circumstances,

  * \- to communicate marketing and promotional offers to our users;
  * \- to provide customer service; and
  * \- to deliver to you information that is targeted to your interests.

Upon receipt of the first communication of this type, you will have the opportunity to opt-out of future communications by following unsubscribe instructions described within the communication. As part of your registration on TFOD, you agree that you may receive certain administrative communications from TFOD in the form of email, within website messages and sms’, and you will not be able to opt out of receiving such administrative communications.

We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent.

However, we may disclose your personal information as follows:

  * \- to affiliates , associates of TFOD that we control and that are subject to this Privacy Policy or follow privacy practices at least as protective measure;
  * \- to third parties to enforce our Terms of Use and other TFOD / ISPL agreements and policies, or to protect anyone's rights, property, or safety;
  * \- to third parties to respond to claims that photos or other content that you upload violates other's rights;
  * \- to an acquirer of all or substantial part of the equity, assets or business of TFOD / ISPL;
  * \- to service providers who help with our business operations and assist in the delivery of TFOD services under obligations of confidentiality;
  * \- to law enforcement or other government officials in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities;

as otherwise required by law.

TFOD / ISPL will not disclose or share any of the user's personally identifiable information except when TFOD / ISPL has the user's permission or under special circumstances, such as when TFOD / ISPL believes in good faith that the law requires it or as permitted in terms of this policy. 

TFOD / ISPL has programmed the website to allow the user to restrict display of his personal contact information. 

TFOD / ISPL may disclose account information in special cases when ISPL has reasons to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating TFOD / ISPL's Terms of Services or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) TFOD / ISPL's rights or property, other TFOD / ISPL network website users, or if TFOD / ISPL deems it necessary to maintain, service, and improve its products and services. Personal information collected may be transferred and shared in the event of a sale.

### Distribution of Information

TFOD / ISPL may, from time to time, send its users emails, sms’ or other communications through different media, regarding its products and services. TFOD / ISPL constantly tries and improves the marketplace tools for better efficiency, more relevancy, innovative business opportunities and better personal preferences. TFOD / ISPL has many match making tools on the marketplace to be used by its users for making relevant business contacts with each other. TFOD / ISPL may allow direct mails using its own scripts (without disclosing the email address) with respect/pertaining to the products and services of third parties that it feels may be of interest to the user or if the user has shown interest in your company for business requirement by way of our special services. All users shall be able to limit / restrict this information sharing through their administration panel available on their ‘Edit Profile’ page. TFOD / ISPL, its registered members or its agents working under confidentiality agreements will send these direct mailers. Relevancy of the contacts made between users would depend upon the information sought & given by various users.

### Updation of Information

A TFOD Member may edit his/her account information and profile by logging onto our website and/or by sending a request to support@tfod.in while a Manufacturer or Service Provider may edit his/her account information and profile by logging onto our website and/or by sending a request to support@tfod.in. The requested changes may take up to 30 days to appear online because of verification process and server cache policies. A user account can be deleted or deactivated, but doing so will result in the user not being able to access any members only area of the network / website. Residual information will / may remain within our archive records.

### Updation of Information

A TFOD Member may edit his/her account information and profile by logging onto our website and/or by sending a request to support@tfod.in while a Manufacturer or Service Provider may edit his/her account information and profile by logging onto our website and/or by sending a request to support@tfod.in. The requested changes may take up to 30 days to appear online because of verification process and server cache policies. A user account can be deleted or deactivated, but doing so will result in the user not being able to access any members only area of the network / website. Residual information will / may remain within our archive records.

### Protection of information

As with all information, TFOD / ISPL does not sell any data in bulk to third party that can be misused for telemarketing or bulk mailing or any other unethical purposes. In addition, TFOD / ISPL does not sell any user's personal information or business information until and unless it is permitted by the user. Any user statistics that we may provide to prospective advertisers or partners regarding product or service usage on TFOD / ISPL network is provided in an aggregate form only and does not include any personally identifiable information about any individual user. We request our users to sign out of their TFOD account and close their browser window when they have finished their work. This is to ensure that others cannot access their personal or business information and correspondence, if the user shares the computer with someone else or is using a computer in a public place. TFOD / ISPL takes necessary steps, within its limits of commercial viability and necessity, to ensure that the user's information is treated in the most secured manner. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while TFOD / ISPL strives to protect the user's personal & business information, it cannot ensure the security of any information transmitted to TFOD / ISPL and you do so at your own risk and liability. Once ISPL receives your transmission / request, it makes best efforts to ensure its security in its systems. Please keep in mind that whenever you post personal & business information online, that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties. 

### Changes in Privacy Policy

The policy may change from time to time so please check periodically.
